<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<application name="addjitter" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://isis.astrogeology.usgs.gov/Schemas/Application/application.xsd">

  <brief>
    Adds harmonic jitter to a cube.
  </brief>

  <description>
    This program will add harmonic jitter to a cube.
  </description>

  <category>
    <categoryItem>Geometry</categoryItem>
  </category>

  <groups>
    <group name="Files">
      <parameter name="FROM">
        <type>cube</type>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Input cube to add harmonic jitter to.
        </brief>
        <description>
          Use this parameter to select the filename. All bands within the file
          will have jitter added in the same way.
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.cub
        </filter>
      </parameter>

      <parameter name="JITTERSOURCE">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Five column CSV with: frequency, sample amplitude, sample phase, line amplitude, line phase
        </brief>
        <description>
          Use this parameter to select the filename that contains the deffinitions of jitter.
          The CSV file should contain 5 columns: frequency, sample amplitude, sample phase, 
          line amplitude, line phase. There is no limit to the number of rows. All rows will be 
          summed to set the total sample and line offsets.
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.csv
        </filter>
      </parameter>

      <parameter name="NORMALLINETABLE">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          CSV with normal readout line numbers and time
        </brief>
        <description>
          Use this parameter to select the filename that contains the normal readout lines only.
          That is all the normal lines without any check lines interspersed. The CSV is (line#, time).
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.csv
        </filter>
      </parameter>

      <parameter name="CHECKLINETABLE">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          CSV with checkline readout line numbers and time
        </brief>
        <description>
          Use this parameter to select the filename that contains the checkline readout lines only.
          Only the checklines and times are in this file. The CSV is (line#, time).
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.csv
        </filter>
      </parameter>
      
      <parameter name="NORMALTO">
        <type>cube</type>
        <fileMode>output</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Output cube
        </brief>
        <description>
          This cube is the full image cube will jitter added.
        </description>
      </parameter>
      
      <parameter name="CHECKLINETO">
        <type>cube</type>
        <fileMode>output</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Output cube
        </brief>
        <description>
          This cube is the checkline cube. The checklines are produced based on the checkline table
          input. This cube is a 
        </description>
      </parameter>
      
      <parameter name="INTERPOLATION">
        <type>string</type>
        <list>
          <option value="CUBICCONVOLUTION"></option>
          <option value="BILINEAR"></option>
        </list>
      </parameter>
    </group>
  </groups>

</application>
