<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<application name="eisCheckTable" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://isis.astrogeology.usgs.gov/Schemas/Application/application.xsd">
  <brief>
    Generates a table that defines order in which lines are read out for EIS rolling shutter camera.
    This application generated three files: the whole table, the normal read out table, and the 
    checkline table. The normal table and the checkline table will use the name of the whole table
    but it will add _normal to the normal table file, and it will add _shadow or _reverse to the checkline
    table according to the checkline type selected.
  </brief>

  <groups>

    <group name="">
      <parameter name="TO">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>output</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Output file where the entire read out table will be written. This filename will serve as 
          the base for the other two files produced, the checkline table, and the normal line table.
        </brief>
      </parameter>
      
      <parameter name="NLINES">
        <type>integer</type>
        <brief>Number of Lines</brief>
        <description>
          This defines how many lines will be extracted from the input cube,
          if LINC is 1. Otherwise, the number of lines actually extracted from 
          the input cube is NLINES/LINC.
        </description>

        <minimum inclusive="yes">1</minimum>
      </parameter>
      
      <parameter name="EXPOSURETIME">
        <type>double</type>
        <brief>The exposure duration of the image without checklines in seconds</brief>
        <description>
        </description>
        <minimum inclusive="yes">0.00000000001</minimum>
      </parameter>
      
      <parameter name="CHECKLINECOUNT">
        <type>integer</type>
        <brief>Number of checklines</brief>
        <description>
          This determines the number of checklines to be added. Each checkline added will increase the 
          overall time it takes to take the entire image including the checklines.
        </description>
        <minimum inclusive="yes">0</minimum>
      </parameter>
      <parameter name="UNIQUECHECKLINES">
        <type>integer</type>
        <brief>The number of distinct checklines</brief>
        <description>
          This is the number of unique checklines. Example: For a 2250 line table, if you choose
          3 repeated checklines the checklines would be 528, 1083, 1638 to evenly distribute over 
          the table. If you have 60 checklines and 3 repeated checklines for a 2250 line table the
          checkline readout would be 528,1083,1638,528,1083,1638... until each unique checkline is 
          repeated 20 times, making 60 checklines total. If you have 60 checklines and 60 unique 
          checklines, each checkline will be unique.
        </description>
      </parameter>
    </group>
  </groups>

</application>
